Hrvoje Sesar

Backend Developer

- ► hrvoje.sesar1411@gmail.com

 → +387 63 204 192

 ← Puringajska 30, 88220 Široki Brijeg

 → hrvoje.sesar1411@gmail.com

 → +387 63 204 192

 ← Puringajska 30, 88220 Široki Brijeg

 → Hrvoje.sesar1411@gmail.com

 → +387 63 204 192

 ← Puringajska 30, 88220 Široki Brijeg

 → Hrvoje.sesar1411@gmail.com

 → +387 63 204 192

 ← Puringajska 30, 88220 Široki Brijeg

 → Hrvoje.sesar1411@gmail.com

 → +387 63 204 192

 ← Puringajska 30, 88220 Široki Brijeg

 → Hrvoje.sesar1411@gmail.com

 → +387 63 204 192

 ← Hrvoje.sesar1411@gmail.com

 → +387 63 204 192

 → +387 64 204 192

 ← Hrvoje.sesar1411@gmail.com

 → +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 192

 ← +387 64 204 1
- in linkedin.com/in/hrvoje-sesar-693034265 🜎 github.com/hrvojesesar

Education

2019 - 2024

Bachelor's and Master's degrees in Computing

Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, Computing and Electrical Engineering, University of Mostar, Mostar

Employment

Jul 2024 - Current

Remote Freelancer

Upwork Global Inc.

- Working on Web Applications, Backend Web Services, Websites
- Using technologies such as: .NET, SQL Server, Laravel, MySQL
- Solving complex problems, including fixing bugs, backend services, third-party integrations
- Preparing technical documentation for delivered projects

Apr 2023 - Jul 2024

Junior Software Developer

Diplomat Tech d.o.o., Široki Brijeg

- Developing modular applications as part of larger software ecosystem
- Using technologies: .NET, MS SQL Server
- Additional refinement on Backend
- Fixing bugs, tasks, code refactoring
- Project documentation
- Agile Development with Scrum and Jira

C#/.NET	JavaScript	MS SQL Server	OOP	Git
PHP/Laravel	HTM5/CSS3	MySQL	REST API	Docker
Java	Bootstrap	PostgreSQL	Microservices	English

C

Projects

Skills

Online Pharmacy

Online Learning Room

Contacts List

Trip Harmony

■ Weather App

SportPro Backoffice

Finance Management App

Fleet Management App

Profile

Junior Backend Developer with proven student intership and work experience helping companies to create and maintain better reusable codebase. Ability to continuously learn and gain experience from senior developers and through various courses. Experience on projects within the faculty doing Backend and Frontend. Passionate about learning and development with a desire to apply skills to more complex and larger projects. I consider myself an ambitious, creative, and communicative person, open to new challenges and opportunities to grow and learn, with problem-solving mindset. Experience with teamwork/group work.